<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="edu.cmu.sei.aaspe.feature"
      label="AASPE Tools"
      version="1.0.0.qualifier">

   <description>
      Automated Assurance of Security Policy Enforcement (AASPE)
About the tools

The AASPE tools are designed for making secure and safe safety-critical systems. The tools are using AADL and the OSATE toolset. It provides the following features:

    Attack Impact meta-model
    Attack Impact graphical editor
    Attack Tree editor meta-model
    Attack Tree graphical editor
    Bridge from Attack Impact to Attack Tree
    Bridge from AADL to Attack Impact
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2016 Carnegie Mellon University.
All Rights Reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      Copyright (c) 2016 Carnegie Mellon University.
All Rights Reserved.
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following acknowledgments and disclaimers.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following acknowledgments and disclaimers in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
3. Products derived from this software may not include “Carnegie Mellon University,” &quot;SEI” and/or “Software Engineering Institute&quot; in the name of such derived product, nor shall “Carnegie Mellon University,” &quot;SEI” and/or “Software Engineering Institute&quot; be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without prior written permission. For written permission, please contact permission@sei.cmu.edu.

ACKNOWLEDGMENTS AND DISCLAIMERS:
This material is based upon work funded and supported by the Department of Defense under Contract No. FA8721-05-C-0003 with Carnegie Mellon University for the operation of the Software Engineering Institute, a federally funded research and development center.

Any opinions, findings and conclusions or recommendations expressed in this material are those of the author(s) and do not necessarily reflect the views of the United States Department of Defense.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS,&quot; WITH NO WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER. CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTEDBY LAW ALL EXPRESS, IMPLIED, AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS.

This material was created under project 5-15-0075R; DFARS 252.204-7000 does not apply.

Carnegie Mellon® is registered in the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office by Carnegie Mellon University.

DM-0003520
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="attackimpact.design"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="attracktree.design"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attackimpact"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attackimpact.actions"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attackimpact.edit"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attackimpact.editor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attackimpact.wizards"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attacktree"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attacktree.edit"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attacktree.editor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.attacktree.wizards"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.codegeneration"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.aaspe.help"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.cmu.sei.aaspe"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
